# PAN YUEHAO

(+65) 9075 3719  $\diamond$  yuehao.pan92@gmail.com  $\diamond$  www.linkedin.com/in/yuehao-pan

Five years' experience in technology consulting, specialized in delivering enterprise technical solution implementations. Cloud advocate who is passionate in data science. Linux Foundation Certified Kubernetes Administrator, Google certified Associate Cloud Engineer and Professional Machine Learning Engineer.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Accenture Pte Ltd

Jul 2015 - Mar 2021

Senior Software Engineering Analyst

Singapore

Project delivery team lead and client-facing consultant, responsible for solution implementation and system maintenance. Proven track record in delivering digital government service projects. Successfully delivered project under Agile development framework.

- · Digital Government Service Transformation
  - Conducted design sessions with clients to study their requirements and the reasons behind the scenes, designed and communicated technical solutions with clients, managed their expectations, and coordinated with users on acceptance testing and business processes to maintain the delivery schedule.
  - Managed clients' requirements and balanced requiring features with release plans, designed solutions under the whole business process to ensure the completeness and feasibility of the solutions, prototyped technical implementations with the development team, and led the team on the innovations to overcome challenges.
  - Implemented internal DevOps solutions, regularized team's branching strategy and code review processes, collaborated with technical operation teams on deployment automation, providing technical base for the Agile development framework.
  - Maintained full-stack web application built on Angular and Spring framework, developed new features, and designed secure infrastructures for app hosting and coexisting, leading to no service disruption during technical cut-over.
  - Monitored and analysed operation data to ensure system's stability for smooth business operations. Organized technical and process-wise strategies to deliver good performance on Bug Bounty Program and annual disaster recovery exercises.

Software Engineering Analyst

Subject matter expert in the app development and server infrastructure team. Experienced in web application development, software architecture design and system integration.

- · Next Generation National Service Portal
  - Developed web portal frontend based on HTML, JavaScript and CSS. Integrated the frontend with WebSphere Content Management System (WCMS) in IBM WebSphere Portal.

- Developed component libraries, content life cycles and access management lists in WCMS, reduced non-technical user's dependencies to maintenance team. Conducted regular training to enable users' ability to manage the system.
- · Client Digital Service Transformation
  - Liaised with stakeholders and successfully on-board client's website on enterprise system built with IBM technology stack.
- · Smart Reading and Analysis Project
  - Successfully developed frontend intelligence feature, and improved process efficiency under tight delivery schedule.

### Institute for Infocomm Research

Aug 2014 - May 2015

Student Researcher

Singapore

Worked on the comparison between classic Neural Networks and multi-layer Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN) applied in real time MRI image data, exploring self-learnt features by visualizing hidden layers in CNN.

- Successfully published research results on IEEE EMBC 2015 conference (Link).

# STARTUP EXPERIENCES

FootySG Apr 2017 – Aug 2018 Co-Founder Singapore

One of the two founders of FootySG, a mobile platform that connects futsal players with field owners. The platform is to prosper Singapore futsal game market. The app had successfully gained over 800 players and 2 business partners after 11 months of the first release. FootySG has been acquired by Rovo on 14<sup>th</sup> Aug 2018 (Link). Main roles include:

- Technical Architect: application development and architecture design for hosting.
- Business Development: setting up pricing strategy, engaging business owners, and promoting the platform to futsal players.

#### **CERTIFICATION**

Certified Kubernetes Administrator	(The Linux Foundation)	Jul 2021
Professional Machine Learning Engineer	$(Google\ Cloud)$	Apr 2021
Associate Cloud Engineer	$(Google\ Cloud)$	Feb 2021
ICAgile Certified Professional	(ICAgile)	Mar 2019

# **EDUCATION**

# National University of Singapore

Aug 2018 – Jun 2020

Master of Science (Statistics)

Singapore

# Nanyang Technological University

Aug 2011 - Jun 2015

Bachelor of Engineering (Information Engineering and Media)

Singapore

- Senior Middle 2 scholarship recipient (Singapore Government Scholarship)